All right, so now we've got a plan document for the authentication forms, and that plan contains all the information, instructions, code examples, and steps needed to implement it.So the next step then is to ask Claude Code to do just that.Now, before we do, I want to talk about two things, starting with model selection.So far, we've been using the Sonic model, right, to make small code changes, create a spec, and also plan the feature, because I think plan mode uses Sonic 4.5 by default as well.
好的，現在我們已經有了身份驗證表單的計畫文件， 這份計畫包含了實作所需的所有資訊、指令、程式碼範例和步驟。 所以下一步就是請 Claude Code 來完成這件事。 在我們開始之前，我想先談兩件事，從模型選擇開始。 到目前為止，我們一直使用的是 Sonnet 模型， 用來進行小幅的程式碼修改、建立規格，以及規劃功能， 因為我認為規劃模式預設也是使用 Sonnet 4.5。
However, when it comes to implementing the plan, I often switch the model to Opus 4.5, or whatever the leading Opus model might be at the time that you're watching this.And that's because the Opus models, especially 4.5 in my experience, are really good at following a set of instructions, like outlined in the plan, and they rarely deviate.So depending on the nature of the feature that I'm working on, I will sometimes choose to work with the Opus model at this point, just by typing the model command.
然而，在實作計畫時，我通常會把模型切換到 Opus 4.5， 或者是你觀看這部影片時當時最新的 Opus 模型。 這是因為 Opus 模型，尤其是 4.5 版本，根據我的經驗， 非常擅長遵循一套指令，就像計畫中所概述的那樣，而且它們很少偏離。 所以根據我正在開發的功能性質， 我有時會在這個時間點選擇使用 Opus 模型，只需輸入 model 指令即可。
and then selecting the Opus 4.5 model.Now for simple features, arguably like this one that we're about to implement, I might stick to Sonnet, but for more in-depth or multi-step or complex features, I would more than likely switch.All right, so next, I want to mention something called extended thinking in Claude Code, which is when the model spends more time reasoning about the task.
然後選擇 Opus 4.5 模型。 對於簡單的功能，就像我們即將實作的這個，我可能會繼續用 Sonnet， 但對於更深入、多步驟或複雜的功能，我很可能會切換。 好的，接下來，我想提到 Claude Code 中一個叫做延伸思考（extended thinking）的功能， 這是讓模型花更多時間思考任務的模式。
Again, this mode is better suited to more complex multi-step problems because it allows the model extra room to explore possible solutions, correct itself, and so on.It does consume more tokens because of that internal reasoning, but it pays dividends when the implementation isn't necessarily straightforward.It also means that if it sees any holes in the plant, it will find an alternative solution.Now, Thinking Mode is actually enabled by default, I think.
同樣地，這個模式更適合更複雜的多步驟問題， 因為它給模型額外的空間來探索可能的解決方案、自我修正等等。 確實，因為內部推理的關係，它會消耗更多 token， 但當實作並不那麼直觀時，它帶來的回報是值得的。 這也意味著如果它發現計畫中有任何漏洞，它會找到替代解決方案。 現在，思考模式預設是開啟的，我想。
And to be honest, unless I'm working on trivial changes, I keep it on most of the time.But you can toggle it on and off by using the Config command and then finding a setting called Thinking Mode.
說實話，除非我在做一些微不足道的變更，否則我大部分時間都保持開啟。 但你可以透過使用 Config 指令， 然後找到名為 Thinking Mode 的設定來開關它。
So, you can see that I've currently got it turned on, which means for all the prompts I currently send, the model will do extra reasoning, producing hopefully better results, but you can toggle it off here by hitting space or enter, and that setting is going to be saved to your global user settings for all projects.Now I'm going to keep mine switched on, but do be wary when using Thinking Mode with Opus 4.5 especially, because it can eat through your token limits a little bit more quickly.
你可以看到我目前已開啟它， 這意味著我目前傳送的所有提示，模型都會進行額外的推理，希望能產出更好的結果。 你可以在這裡按空白鍵或 Enter 來關閉它， 這個設定會儲存到你所有專案的全域使用者設定中。 我會繼續保持開啟，但要特別注意搭配 Opus 4.5 使用思考模式時， 因為它可能會更快消耗你的 token 限額。
On a Mac, I can also toggle Thinking Mode on and off quickly by pressing Option + T, which brings the option to turn it on or off.On Windows, I think you'll need to press Alt + T instead.Also, if you have Thinking Mode turned off by default, you can trigger extended thinking in a single exchange or prompt by typing the word UltraThink into your messages.I could type out my regular prompt and then tell it to UltraThink about it at the end, and that would trigger thinking mode for that prompt.
在 Mac 上，我也可以按 Option + T 快速開關思考模式，它會帶出開啟或關閉的選項。 在 Windows 上，我想你需要改按 Alt + T。 另外，如果你預設關閉了思考模式， 你可以在單次對話或提示中輸入 UltraThink 這個詞來觸發延伸思考。 我可以打出我的一般提示，然後在最後告訴它 UltraThink， 這樣就會為那個提示觸發思考模式。
Anyway, I'm going to keep thinking mode on for this, and I've also switched to OPUS 4.5, which might be overkill for this feature, but I wanted to show you my typical workflow.And now I'm going to make sure the plan document is open to supply it automatically as context to cloud code, and then I'll type, Can you implement this plan?
無論如何，我要為這個保持思考模式開啟， 我也已切換到 Opus 4.5，雖然對這個功能來說可能有點大材小用， 但我想展示我的典型工作流程。 現在我要確保計畫文件是開啟的，這樣它就會自動作為上下文提供給 Claude Code， 然後我輸入：「你能實作這個計畫嗎？」
And then just hit enter.So when I do that, the model is going to look through the plan, a reason about how best to implement it, and then go ahead and start making code changes.Now, normally as well, I also put auto edit mode on.So let's do that.And to speed this process up, I'm going to just fast forward the video, grant any permissions it might need, and then I'll come back at the end when it's done so we can walk through the results together.
然後按下 Enter。 這樣做之後，模型會看過計畫，推理如何以最佳方式實作它， 然後開始進行程式碼變更。 通常，我也會同時開啟自動編輯模式，就讓我們這樣做吧。 為了加速這個過程，我要加速播放影片，授予它可能需要的任何權限， 然後等它完成後回來，這樣我們就能一起看結果。
All right, so that took two and a half minutes to complete for all of those components created.And if we take a look at all this, you can see it's created all these new components.It's updated these pages.It's created all the new test files.They all pass now.There was some kind of error up here.I think it was a linting error, so it did that and then it went ahead and fixed it as well.So it does iterate on problems when it comes across them.So let's now have a look at the new files it's added.
好的，建立所有那些元件總共花了兩分半鐘。 如果我們看一下這些內容，你可以看到它建立了所有這些新元件、更新了這些頁面， 並建立了所有新的測試檔案，它們現在全部通過了。 上面有某種錯誤，我認為是 linting 錯誤，它發現後就去修復了。 所以它確實在遇到問題時會反覆嘗試解決。 那麼現在讓我們來看看它新增的檔案。
Just very briefly, and again, I'm not going to spend a long time on this for the sake of this tutorial, because I really don't think you want to watch me just going through files.But I would normally spend a good half an hour or so, maybe longer, going through the different files it's created, making sure everything looks correct to me,Making sure I understand everything, because I would hate for a project to spiral into a direction where I don't really know what's going on, so I'm going to quickly have a little look at these components.
只是非常簡短地看一下，同樣地，為了這個教學，我不會在這上面花太長時間， 因為我真的不認為你想看我一直瀏覽檔案。 但我通常會花半個小時左右，也許更長， 逐一看過它建立的不同檔案，確認所有內容對我來說都是正確的， 確保我理解所有內容， 因為我不希望專案朝著一個我不清楚發生什麼事的方向發展， 所以我要快速看一下這些元件。
We've got a button component, first of all, here with three different files, so it looks pretty simple.We've got some props right here and a prop interface, so...The type is either submit, reset, or button.Then we have the children, which is whatever text I guess we pass into the button, an on click handler that is passed forward, and a disabled prop as well.So this is all quite simple.
首先是按鈕元件，這裡有三個不同的檔案，看起來很簡單。 這裡有一些 props 和 prop 介面， type 是 submit、reset 或 button 其中之一。 然後是 children，就是我們傳入按鈕的文字， 一個往前傳遞的 onClick 處理器，以及一個 disabled prop。 所以這一切都相當簡單。
And then we've got a class name here of BTM, which is one we already created, plus the styles for this particular button as well.All right, cool.So that's the button, very simple.The input component is here.Again, we've got some props.typed up here.Again, very simple.And we start it up here using the input group.So let's have a look at this.Yep, that is the input group class there inside the module.And then down here we have the label for the inputs, which we can pass in.
然後這裡有一個 class name 為 BTM，這是我們已經建立的， 加上這個特定按鈕的樣式。好的，很棒。所以按鈕就這樣，非常簡單。 輸入元件在這裡，同樣有一些 props，也很簡單。 我們在這裡用 input group 開始。讓我們看一下這個， 是的，那就是模組裡的 input group class。 然後往下這裡是輸入的標籤，我們可以傳入它。
And also the input itself with the on change handler, the class.Okay, yeah, all looks pretty good.
還有輸入本身，帶有 onChange 處理器和 class。 好的，看起來都很不錯。
The login form itself.All right, so yeah, standard react components andAnd then down here we're using a bit of state for the e-mail and password.We have a submit handler.We prevent the default action.And then we log the e-mail and password to the console.Then we're using those input components and the password input, which we've not seen yet.And then the button component at the bottom.We also have that link to the signup page.Good.And let's have a look at the signup form first of all, before we look at the password input.
登入表單本身。好的，就是標準的 React 元件， 往下我們用了一點 state 來處理電子郵件和密碼。 我們有一個提交處理器，阻止預設動作，然後將電子郵件和密碼輸出到主控台。 然後我們使用那些輸入元件和密碼輸入（我們還沒看到的那個）， 以及底部的按鈕元件。 我們也有連到註冊頁面的連結。很好。 在我們看密碼輸入之前，先來看看註冊表單。
So this looks pretty similar.We're using state again.We've got the submit handler, does a similar thing.Yeah, they all look pretty similar, except this one now goes to the login page at the bottom.All right.And then we also have the password input component right here.And we're taking all these props, same as the other inputs, but this time we have this bit of state, visible and set visible.
這看起來很相似。我們再次使用 state。 我們有提交處理器，做類似的事情。 是的，它們看起來都很相似，只是這個在底部換成了連到登入頁面。 好的。然後我們還有這裡的密碼輸入元件。 我們接收所有這些 props，跟其他輸入一樣， 但這次我們有這個 state：visible 和 setVisible。
So we should have an icon here somewhere, shouldn't we?There it is.So we have the eye off and also the eye.
所以我們應該在某個地方有一個圖示，不是嗎？ 找到了。我們有 EyeOff 和 Eye。
When we click on one of these, which is actually a button, it's embedded inside a button, when we click on that, it's toggling the visibility, this bit of state.So it's either going to show one or the other.And when we have, there's the input, so when we have visible set to true, then it is going to show the text inside it.It's going to become a text input basically.Now whenthe visible is false, it's gonna become a password import and therefore hide it.
當我們點擊其中一個圖示——它其實是一個按鈕，嵌入在一個按鈕裡—— 點擊後會切換這個 state 的可見性，所以它會顯示其中一個或另一個。 當 visible 設定為 true 時，它會顯示其中的文字，基本上它會變成一個文字輸入框。 而當 visible 為 false 時，它會變成一個密碼輸入框，從而隱藏文字。
Okay, yeah, that all makes sense to me.All right, so what else have we got?We've got the test down here, which I don't think we really need to take a look at.It's created test files for each of these.Again, I would go through these if I wasn't recording a video.And then up here inside the app folder, we should have those components added to the login page, which we do, the login form right here, and also the signup page right here.
好的，這對我來說都說得通。好的，我們還有什麼？ 下面有測試，我認為我們不太需要去看它。 它為每一個元件都建立了測試檔案，同樣地，如果我不是在錄影，我會去看這些。 然後在 app 資料夾裡面，我們應該有那些元件加入到登入頁面， 確實有，這裡是登入表單，還有這裡的註冊頁面。
All right, awesome, so it all looks good to me, and what I would do now is just preview this in a browser.All right then, so here we are on the login page, and that all looks pretty good to me, so I could type something in here like mario@, I don't know, pocketheist.com, and down here we've got the password, test1234.If I click on this icon, this eye icon, then we can see it, and yeah, that's all working, pretty nice.
好的，太棒了，看起來一切都不錯，我現在要做的就是在瀏覽器中預覽一下。 好的，我們在登入頁面上，看起來都很好， 我可以在這裡輸入一些東西，比如 mario@，不知道，pocketheist.com， 然後下面我們輸入密碼 test1234。 如果我點擊這個圖示，這個眼睛圖示，就可以看到密碼了。 嗯，一切都運作正常，滿不錯的。
We can switch to the sign up page over here, which again looks okay to me.So let's just make sure this works as well.So mario@ph.com and then create a password, test1234.So by default it doesn't show.If we click on the eye icon, then it does show and vice versa.Awesome.Okay then, so that's all looking good to me.All right then, so because I'm happy with this at this moment, I would probably now go ahead and addadd all these changes to staging.So let me do that over here.
我們可以在這裡切換到註冊頁面，看起來也不錯。 讓我們確認這個也運作正常。輸入 mario@ph.com，然後建立密碼 test1234。 預設情況下它不顯示。如果我們點擊眼睛圖示，它就會顯示，反之亦然。太棒了。 好的，看起來一切都很好。 因為我現在對這個感到滿意，我可能會把這些變更全部加入暫存區。 讓我在這裡這樣做。
I'll just say git add.And then I'm going to go ahead and use the commit message command to make a commit.So let's do that.Commit hyphen message down here and press enter.And then that's going to commit that to this branch right here, which remember we're working on, which is Claude forward slash feature forward slash authentication forms.So it's made the message for us.I will say yes, I want you to commit with that message.So then my friends, we've now completed a full cycle of this workflow.
我就說 git add。然後我要使用 commit message 指令來做一次提交。 就這樣做，在這裡輸入 commit -m 然後按 Enter。 這樣就會把它提交到這個分支—— 記得我們正在使用的是 claude/feature/authentication-forms 這個分支。 它為我們生成了提交訊息，我說是的，請用那個訊息提交。 好了各位朋友，我們現在完成了這個工作流程的完整一個循環。
We have made a high level feature spec using the spec command.Then we made a detailed technical plan about how to implement that feature.And finally, we used that plan to add the feature with Open 4.5 and extended thinking.Now, like I said earlier, you can add more steps to this workflow to include maybe design references, code reviews, et cetera.And we will be doing some of that later on.But even without those, I think this is a solid, simple three-step process.You cancould use to start adding features to the application.
我們使用 spec 指令建立了一份高層次的功能規格， 然後我們制定了一份關於如何實作該功能的詳細技術計畫， 最後，我們用那份計畫搭配 Opus 4.5 和延伸思考功能來新增該功能。 就像我之前說的，你可以為這個工作流程加入更多步驟， 也許包括設計參考、程式碼審查等等，我們之後也會做一些這樣的事。 但即使沒有這些，我認為這是一個穩固、簡單的三步驟流程， 你可以用它開始為應用程式新增功能。
Now, at this point, I would normally push this feature branch to GitHub so it could be reviewed and then merged into the main branch.But I don't want to introduce GitHub to the workflow just yet because there's going to be a whole chapter about that later on.So for now, because I'm fully happy with this feature implementation, I'll just merge this branch locally by coming to the chat window and entering bash mode.Then I'm going to switch to the main branch by typing git switch main and hitting enter.
到這個時間點，我通常會把這個功能分支推送到 GitHub， 讓它可以被審查後合併到主分支。 但我現在還不想在工作流程中引入 GitHub， 因為後面會有一整個章節專門介紹它。 所以現在，因為我對這個功能的實作完全滿意， 我就在本地合併這個分支，來到對話框並進入 bash 模式， 然後輸入 git switch main 按下 Enter 切換到主分支。
Once we're on the main branch, we can enter bash mode again and then merge the feature branch by tapping git, merge, and then whatever the branch name is that we want to merge into main.And once we've done that, we can just hit enter to run the command and merge the feature branch into the main one so it contains that new feature that we just added.Alright my friends, so that is the end of this free chapter.I really, really hope you gained something from it.
一旦切換到主分支，我們可以再次進入 bash 模式， 然後輸入 git merge，再加上我們想要合併到主分支的分支名稱，來合併功能分支。 完成後，我們就可以按下 Enter 執行指令， 將功能分支合併到主分支，讓主分支包含我們剛剛新增的新功能。 好了，各位朋友，這就是這個免費章節的結尾。 我真的非常希望你從中有所收穫。
And like I said before, this was just a tiny part of the full Claude Code masterclass that I recently released on netninja.dev.So if you enjoyed this and you want to learn much more about the process and extend the process,and also learn about other topics like MCP servers, sub-agents, and the newer Claude Code web tool, then definitely check this course out.It's only $15, and if you use the promo code ClaudeNinja, you can get the course for half price, but that code is going to expire in a few weeks.
就像我之前說的，這只是我最近在 netninja.dev 發布的 完整 Claude Code 大師課程的一小部分。 如果你喜歡這個並想深入了解這個流程、延伸這個流程， 以及學習 MCP 伺服器、子代理和更新的 Claude Code 網頁工具等其他主題， 那一定要去看看這門課程。 只要 15 美元，而且如果你使用優惠碼 ClaudeNinja 可以以半價購買， 但那個優惠碼將在幾週後過期。
Also, if you want access to my entire course library, including this Claude Code masterclass, plus nine other masterclass courses, as well as other exclusive tutorials, you can sign up for a NetNinja Pro subscription.It's just $9 a month, and you can get your first month half price using thispromo code right here.Anyway, I really hope you enjoyed this chapter and I'm going to see you all in the next series.
另外，如果你想存取我的整個課程庫， 包括這門 Claude Code 大師課程、另外九門大師課程，以及其他獨家教學， 你可以訂閱 NetNinja Pro。 每月只要 9 美元，而且使用這裡的優惠碼，你可以以半價享受第一個月。 無論如何，我真的希望你喜歡這個章節，我們下個系列見。